# **ANNISA GITA**

Address: Jakarta, Indonesia | Phone: 0822 7937 6080 email: annisagita.work@gmail.com | linkedin: linkedin.com/in/annisagita/

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Had 1.5+ years of experience in database analysis, design, mobile application development, project management, software testing, and technical writing. I am interested in people management, technology, and everything that can bring impact for helping other people. Feel free to connect on any excellent opportunity.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Junior Project Manager

Mar, 2021 - Jun, 2022

Solusi Teknologi Nusantara (NUSANTECH)

- Re-manage projects which not been monitored before and created documentation
- Conduct multiple project management cycles, and analyze project issues.
- Communicating with internal and external stakeholders for managing client expectations and reporting.
- Feature prioritization and organizing for offline and online teams to work efficiently and effectively.
- Database analysis and data mapping and do software testing and documentation.

Project: Created student admission system for one of the ministries and an internal dashboard for a company in the financial sector

Product: Website for Educational startups

Part of Project : Testing and presentation for e-learning one of BUMN bank and Planning phase for EOffice for one of Government agency

# **Lab Assistant for Software Project**

Jun, 2020 - Aug, 2020

Sumatra Institute of Technology

- Supervise and guide multiple project teams, in carrying out the project can complete on time.
- Conduct weekly meetings for reviews and retrospectives in each sprint, giving scores and evaluations to each member in the project.
- Produce a project that is and all members can pass the course.

# Information Technology Intern

Jun, 2019 - Aug, 2019

General Secretariat of DPR RI

- Manage team and projects from start to finish.
- Translate requirements into WBS and create a timeline.
- Monitoring project with daily meeting and use Github for development of an android app and integration with API.

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Bachelor of Computer Science**

2016 - 2020

Sumatra Institute of Technology

First graduate class of 2016 (GPA: 3.17 / 4.00)

Thesis: Expert system for detecting anxiety disorders by DSM IV

• Part of ITERA 3 Dies Natalis documentation team (2017), ITERA Startup Conference design team (2017), ITERA Film Festival (2017) and active in other campus activities.

#### CERTIFICATION AND TRAINING

#### Become a Product Manager

Now

**Udemy Course** 

#### Certificate of Competence in IT Multimedia

Oct, 2020

Badan Sertifikasi Komputer Nasional | Credential ID ICT 294 00010394 2020

#### **Software Product Management**

Sep, 2020

Coursera (University of Alberta) | Credential ID JTH26EE5XVXJ

#### SKILL

Web Application | Project Management | Communication | Problem Solving | Product Development | IT Solution | Dashboard Application | Al | Data Analysis | Public Speaking | SDLC | Scrum

#### ORGANIZATION

# **Executive Council of Student (KM ITERA)**

Oct, 2017 - Jan, 2020

Sumatra Institute of Technology

General treasurer (2018 - 2020)

Manage finances at km itera, collect cash, make financial records of cash flow cycles and succeed in reporting cabinet finances at the end of the term of office

Division of communication and information (2017 - 2018)

Being part of the communication and information staff staff contributed to the devotion of the ITERA student council activities.

## **Electro and Informatic Student Council (HMEI)**

Feb, 2017 - Mei, 2019

Sumatra Institute of Technology

Alumni Coordinator (2018 - 2019)

Become part of the alumni coordinator who successfully organized the activities of forming an electrical alumni association and information alumni association. As well as carrying out duties as a member of the external division well.